export const description: { [key: string]: string } = {
  hoarding: `Hoardings in {{city}} improve long-term brand recall and offer wide reach. They are typically found in hyperlocal areas with large crowds which offer high visibility to passersby, pedestrians, and commuters. As people quickly notice them, Hoardings attract potential customers and maintain brand awareness. Hoarding Ads are generally used to showcase new products/services/offers.`,
  busShelter: `Bus shelters in {{city}} provide an excellent advertising opportunity due to their strategic locations along busy streets and near public transportation stops. They offer exposure to pedestrians and commuters waiting for buses, thereby ensuring high visibility for advertisements displayed on them.`,
  unipole: `Unipole advertisements in {{city}} are single-sided structures often installed along major roads and highways. They offer excellent visibility to vehicular traffic, making them effective for promoting brands and products to motorists. Unipoles are typically illuminated for increased visibility during the day and night.`,
  billboard: `Billboard advertisements in {{city}} are large, prominent structures strategically placed in high-traffic areas. These billboards offer maximum visibility to both vehicular and pedestrian traffic, making them ideal for brand promotion and product advertising. They are often illuminated to ensure visibility at all times, day or night, enhancing the impact of your message. Billboards can accommodate a variety of creative designs, allowing for dynamic and engaging content. Their large size ensures that your advertisement stands out even from a distance. Additionally, the high placement of billboards helps in capturing the attention of a broader audience, making them a powerful tool for reaching potential customers.`,
};

export const quesAndAns = {
  hoarding: [
    {
      question: "What is Hoarding Advertising in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Hoardings in {{city}} improve long-term brand recall and offer wide reach. They are typically found in hyperlocal areas with large crowds which offer high visibility to passersby, pedestrians, and commuters. As people quickly notice them, Hoardings attract potential customers and maintain brand awareness. Hoarding Ads are generally used to showcase new products/services/offers.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Hoarding Advertisement in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Hoarding Advertisement in {{city}} is a form of outdoor advertising which takes many forms and features branding and other business information. Hoarding Advertisement in {{city}} offers high visibility depending on their positioning and size. Place Your Hoarding Ads Now!",
    },
    {
      question: "What are the benefits of Hoarding Ads in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Hoardings are one of the oldest forms of advertising and help improve brand positioning as well as demand generation. Hoardings offer brands a good return on investment by generating valuable leads. Calculate Your Return On Investment With TMA!",
    },
    {
      question: "How effective are Hoarding Ads in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Due to its size and placement, Hoarding Ads in {{city}} are hard to miss. Typically, Ads in Hoardings are used by brands looking to market new products or services. Hoarding Ads in {{city}} are big display ads that will showcase the brand to a large-scale audience that will benefit the company image and build awareness for them. Hoardings help companies promote their brands and amplify reach using engaging content.",
    },
    {
      question: "What are Billboard Ads?",
      answer:
        "Billboard Ads are one of the most popular outdoor advertising options that will help build awareness of the brand.",
    },
    {
      question: "What are the Hoarding Advertising Rates in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Hoarding Advertising Rates in {{city}} may vary depending on what is quoted by the vendor. Various Hoarding Advertising placement options are available at discounted rates, out of which brands and companies can select according to their requirements. Our pricing models for Hoarding Advertising Rates in {{city}} are some of the best in the market offering advertisers some of the best options for Hoarding advertising.",
    },
  ],
  busShelter: [
    {
      question: "What is Bus Shelter Advertising in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Bus Shelter Ads in {{city}} will build brand awareness and recall among potential customers. These are out-of-home advertising tools targeting people who are waiting for their buses to arrive, commuting on the road, or just passing by. Bus Shelters are displayed repeatedly, and due to their frequency, ads in bus shelters are a good cost-effective option for wide reach and establishing brand familiarity.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Bus Shelter Advertisement in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Bus Shelter Advertisement in {{city}} is a cost-effective way to advertise your business to a local audience. Ads in Bus Shelter will help companies build high demand for new products or services. Using the Bus Shelter Advertisement in {{city}}, brands can build a strong impact for the onlookers. Being a cost-effective medium of marketing, ads in Bus Shelter help target specific geographical locations and people stuck in traffic or moving in traffic will also be able to see it.",
    },
    {
      question: "How effective are Bus Shelter Ads in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Bus Shelter Ads in {{city}} effectively and efficiently cater to a large reach and improve brand awareness among a wide audience demographic. Using location-based targeting, advertisements in Bus Shelter will target potential customers from different walks of life. Bus Shelter Ads in {{city}} are mainly high-traffic sheltered waiting areas for commuters waiting for their bus to arrive. These ads in Bus Shelters will help display promotional advertisements in curated locations in heavy-traffic areas.",
    },
    {
      question: "What are the Bus Shelter Advertising Rates in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Bus Shelter Ads Rates in {{city}} may vary depending on what is quoted by the vendor and the location of the advertisement. Various Bus Shelter Advertising placement options are available at discounted rates, out of which brands and companies can select according to their requirements. Ad rates for Bus Shelters in {{city}} depend on the customizations made to it. Our pricing models for Bus Shelter Advertising Rates in {{city}} are some of the best in the market offering advertisers some of the best options for Bus Shelter Ads Rates in {{city}}.",
    },
  ],
  unipole: [
    {
      question: "What is Unipole Advertising in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Unipole Branding in {{city}} is the front-runner in the field of the outdoor campaign. It is considered the most cost-effective branding that gives high brand exposure. Advertising here helps in targeting regular commutes through a creative approach. This flexible medium allows brands to get high visibility in prominent locations. Unipole Advertising offers brands wide range visibility and are a cost-effective way to promote brand products, services or seasonal offers. Unipole Advertising in {{city}} will help companies improve their brand recall through repetitive advertising. Through back to back placements at a short distance, Pole Branding promotes brand popularity and reach. Unipole Ads are spread across the city that will create a lasting impression among potential customers. Through Unipole Advertising in {{city}} brands can lead their audience. Place Your Pole Branding Now.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Unipole Advertisement in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Unipole Advertisement in {{city}} is a growing outdoor advertising medium that enables advertisers to communicate their message efficiently and creatively. Unipole Ads are one of the most commonly seen forms of outdoor advertisement, they can be seen on major city roads or at traffic intersections. Unipole Advertisement in {{city}} is small and compact panels consisting of back-to-back advertising boards which are installed on electric poles that are placed along the roadside or footpaths.",
    },
    {
      question: "How effective are Unipole Ads in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Unipole Ads in {{city}} are one of the most efficient ways of advertising on outdoor platforms. Usually found in places with high traffic, Unipole Ads leave an impression among potential customers. Ads in Unipole have attractive creatives that will draw attention through strategically placed display ads. Unipole Ads in {{city}} are found on major city roads with small and compact advertising panels placed on electric poles. Advertising in Pole Kiosks has many benefits, including being one of the most commonly seen advertising mediums, affordable rates for both advertisers and owners, and flexibility in designing your own poster or banner adds to the benefit of doing ads on pole kiosks.",
    },
    {
      question: "What are the Unipole Advertising Rates in {{city}}?",
      answer:
        "Unipole Advertising Rates in {{city}} may vary depending on what is quoted by the vendor and the location of the advertisement. Various Unipole Advertising placement options are available at discounted rates, out of which brands and companies can select according to their requirements. Ad rates for Unipole in {{city}} depend on the customizations made to it. Our pricing models for Ads on Unipole in {{city}} are some of the best in the market offering advertisers some of the best options for Unipole Ads Rates in {{city}}. Unipole Advertisement Rates in {{city}} will also vary according to the number of Pole Kiosks and the duration for which the advertisement will be displayed. Ads in Pole Kiosks are an affordable transit advertising tactic that can help improve brand awareness.",
    },
  ],
};
